Exercise 6-12, 30 little turtles in a bottle of bottled water. Repeat the
following paragraph focusing on the consonant plus ol combinations. This
paragraph was quoted in the New York Times by Pulitzer Prize winning journalist
Thomas Friedman. Thirty little turtles in a bottle of bottled water. A bottle of
bottled water held thirty little turtles. It didn't matter that each turtle had to
rattle a metal ladle in order to get a little noodles, a total turtle
delicacy. The problem was that there were many turtle battles for the less the
noodles of noodles. The littlest turtles always lost because every time they
thought about grappling with the bigger turtles, their little turtle minds boggled
and they only caught a little noodles.